https://www.raidinc.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Privacy Statement | RAID Inc.
Talk To An Expert
Search for:
Accelerate Time to Insight
RAID Inc. high-performance file system solutions are fully-optimized to accelerate AI applications for greatest productivity. Our customers benefit from flexible configurations that scale, lower TCO and expert services to keep your platforms at peak performance.
Learn More
Company
About
Blog
Careers
Contact
Customers
News & Events
Our 6 Step Holistic Process
Using our time-tested, six-step holistic process, we collaborate with customers to understand their unique challenges and then design, develop, implement and support the best high-performance storage solutions – all seamlessly integrated into existing infrastructure.
Learn More
Solutions
Lustre on ZFS
Lustre
Quick Links
Sales
Email Sales
Talk to an Expert
RAID Inc. + Lustre on ZFS Solutions
ZFS is a robust, scalable file-system with features not available in other file systems. RAID Inc. offers highly-customized Lustre on ZFS solutions to enable cost-effective, more reliable storage for Lustre while maintaining high performance.
Learn More
Products
File Storage
Xanadu 510EL
Xanadu X-AI Series
Block Storage
Xanadu 510ES
ARI 200 Series
Ability 4U 90-Bay JBOD at $37,000
The Ability 4U 90-Bay JBOD boasts 900 TB of raw storage, FIPS-2 Compliance and 3 years of industry-leading RAIDserv support, including next-day parts replacement, firmware updates and 24×7 telephone support. In stock now. Quantities are limited.
Learn More
Products
File Storage
Xanadu 510EL
Xanadu X-AI Series
Block Storage
ARI 200 Series
ARI 400 Series
Ability 4U 90-Bay JBOD at $37,000
The Ability 4U 90-Bay JBOD boasts 900 TB of raw storage, FIPS-2 Compliance and 3 years of industry-leading RAIDserv support, including next-day parts replacement, firmware updates and 24×7 telephone support. In stock now. Quantities are limited.
Learn More
Privacy Policy
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy
General Information
RAID Inc. respects the privacy of our customers, business partners, employees and job applicants, and other visitors to our websites who may choose to provide personal information. We recognize the need for appropriate protections and management of personal information that you provide to us. This Privacy Statement will assist you to understand what types of information we may collect, how that information may be used, and with whom the information may be shared.
What Personal Information does RAID Inc. Collect?
Personal Information is information that can be used to identify or contact a specific individual, such as a name, address, telephone number or email address. RAID Inc. may collect certain personal information from customers, business partners, employees and candidates for employment. RAID Inc. does not collect personal information when you visit RAID Inc.’s web sites unless you choose to provide such personal information.
Customers and Partners
On the RAID Inc. website you can request quotes for products and services, register products, request information, subscribe to marketing or support materials, login to a secure support site to obtain access to product information, support and services, or apply for jobs at RAID Inc. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, user IDs and passwords, and contact preferences.
How does RAID Inc. Use Personal Information?
RAID Inc. will use personal information to provide customers and business partners with information and services and to help us better understand your needs and interests. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction or order, to communicate with you, to deliver products/services to you, to bill you for products/services you purchased, and to provide ongoing service and support. Occasionally we may use your information to contact you to complete surveys that we use for marketing and quality assurance purposes. Personal information collected online may be combined with information you provide to RAID Inc. through other sources such as trade shows or seminars.
To the extent that RAID Inc. uses personal information to email you about our product and services, RAID Inc.’s email practices are in compliance with the U.S. and E.U. SPAM laws. Information about the U.S. and E.U. SPAM laws can be found here.
RAID Inc. also uses personal information to identify and consider candidates for employment opportunities within RAID Inc. RAID Inc. uses personal information about its employees in connection with the administration of its Human Resources programs and functions and for the purpose of communicating with its employees.
Except as provided in this Statement, RAID Inc. does not use your personal information for a purpose other than the stated purpose for which such information is collected.
With Whom does RAID Inc. Share Personal Information?
RAID Inc. may share personal information with its service providers and suppliers for the sole purpose and only to the extent needed to support the customers’ business needs. Service providers and suppliers are required to keep confidential the personal information received from RAID Inc. and may not use it for any purpose other than as originally intended. Third party vendors, service providers and suppliers receiving personal information are expected to apply the same level of privacy protection as contained in this Privacy Statement.
Except as provided above, RAID Inc. will not share personal information with any other third parties without your permission. RAID Inc. will not sell, trade or lease your personal information to others.
Choice and Consent
RAID Inc. does not require that customers, business partners or non-employee visitors to RAID Inc. websites provide RAID Inc. with personal information. The decision to provide personal information is voluntary. If you do not wish to provide the personal information requested, however, you may not be able to proceed with the activity or receive the benefit for which the personal information is being requested. Except as expressly stated otherwise in this Privacy Statement, you may opt out of having RAID Inc. share personal information with third parties as described in this Privacy Statement by notifying RAID Inc. in writing of your desire to do so.
Access to and Accuracy of Your Information
RAID Inc. strives to keep your personal information accurate. We have implemented technology, management processes and policies to maintain data integrity. We will provide you with access to your information, including making reasonable effort to provide you with online access and the opportunity to change your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to your data.
Verification
RAID Inc. will engage in periodic self-assessment to verify that it continues to be in compliance with this Privacy Statement.
Changes to this Statement
RAID Inc. will review and update this Statement periodically, and will note the date of its most recent revision below.
© 2020 RAID Inc.
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Contact
